mormonboyz.com 2019-11-17

# Privacy Policy MissionaryBoys.com

Your privacy is important to us here at missionaryBoyz. To protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted to missionaryBoyz.com (MBz). On some pages, you can purchase a Membership to Mbz, make requests, and register to receive access and materials. The type of personal information collected at these pages are name, age, email address, gender, etc.

We use CCBill, who will obtain additional information such as your address and credit card data.

The information collected by MBz is used solely for the creation and maintenance of your Membership account. We do not sell, loan, lease, swap, trade or otherwise disclose your personal data. That information collected by CCBill is used for the purpose of processing payment of your Membership to MBz.

You can access all your personally identifiable information that CCBill collects online and maintain it by logging on to the right user account pages through CCBill’s website, where the informations was collected. We do not keep your information on our server to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information simply by modifying that information online on CCBill’s website.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online through MBz.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access to MBz.

You as the Member assure MBz that you have all rights for the submission of your data to the member management and payment processor system employed by MBz. You agree to save harmless MBz from all costs, which result from offenses against it.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us by following the instructions on the [Contact Me](http://www.missionaryboyz.com/contact/) page.

Copyright © 2019 Charged Media All Rights Reserved. Unauthorized reproduction or distribution of any component of this site, in whole or in part, is a violation of applicable federal copyright laws and international copyright treaties.  
For billing support, please visit [segpay.com](https://cs.segpay.com/) | [epoch.com](https://epoch.com/) | [ccbill.com](https://www.ccbill.com/), our authorized sales agents.
